hey everyone thanks for listening to the
grow your life podcast my name is
jeremiah krakowski if you haven't
listened to this podcast before i've
been helping business owners for the
last 19 years grow their businesses
online to get more customers and make
more money using the tools of direct
response marketing now i help course
creators coaches trainers authors
speakers
anybody that wants to sell products
online specifically digital products or
information products but this can also
apply to any sort of online business
including e-commerce network marketing
and other forms of business online and
what i want to do is i want to help you
get more results we've helped build
businesses to tens of millions of
dollars from scratch and so if you're
somebody that's just getting started
you're in the right place listen my
friends this is going to be the
definitive guide to your sales funnel
now i have over 160 podcast episodes on
the grow your life podcast if you check
out over my website they cover a variety
of topics they cover
so many topics in fact that sometimes it
can be overwhelming if you go to my
youtube channel as well i have all just
under 1 000 videos if i go over here to
my my youtube
you can see this if you're watching the
video version you can see what i'm
actually pulling up on my screen if you
search for my name jeremiah krakowski
and any topic about what i'm talking
about you're going to find these videos
now i'm going to create a list in the
description if you go under the video in
youtube
i'm going to create a list of supporting
videos that talk about the different
topics that i'm sharing today and i'm
going to have those so you can go
through those in your own time as well
you can search in the youtube search
that's where you're going to find some
of the best videos on these different
topics okay so for your for your offer
um for your
guide to selling more with ads and
online offers for your sales and all of
that but what i'm gonna do today is i'm
gonna break down start to finish
for you the sales funnel process
from ad to sale okay
and so what it is is we start right here
and i want to sort of paint a picture
this is what we call the customer
journey
this is the ether right here okay this
is uh it's about eight eight billion
people
on planet earth okay so that's eight
billion people out here over on this end
right
and then right here
is
your customers let's say you have let's
say
initially you have 3 000 people or let's
let's make it simple 300 right 300
customers is a good start even 30 is a
good start don't get overwhelmed by
these big numbers
we help people make their first five
thousand dollars their first ten
thousand dollars and but oftentimes when
people work with me and they really
start to get this process they don't
stop there they end up going to 30 to 50
to 100 000 a month and i'm telling you
making a million dollars or a half a
million dollars doing what i'm showing
you right now is not out of the question
i had somebody this week on my social
media telling me that well you're
talking about the one percent of the one
percent of people and i'm saying yeah
but
they just don't know how to do it right
they don't know how to get more
customers the effective way and so what
i'm going to show you is the most
effective way to get
customers for any business okay
so we start with the ether of people
eight billion people and i'm gonna break
this down really fast and then i'm gonna
break down each step as we go along it
so so if you feel like i'm going over
this a little too quickly for you to
follow
um just keep watching and i'm gonna
break down each step on this
so we start with these people and what
we have is we have platforms okay
so we have
uh
facebook
we have uh tick tock
we have
instagram and most of what we talk about
deals with social media social media
sales you also do have though you have
your your blog
this is your own website
which is generally actually starts with
google
or
referrals
you have
your email list or other people's email
list
other people's email lists right
so these are platforms
that either other people or you have
built
with people
from these eight billion people
the ones that are on the internet are
the ones that you're going to reach and
what i specifically teach is about using
the internet so we're not talking about
like
finding people
that
want to coach with you that are not
online and you meet them at a coffee
shop somewhere
that type of networking there's a lot of
great training out there on that i'm not
really the guy that's going to teach you
a lot of that
because i just find it's a lot easier to
find people through the internet okay
and so
these are platforms
where people exist
where they they interact with their
friends they interact with their family
members okay
and so on these platforms
your your your 300 customers let's just
say it's like your dream 300 or your
dream 100
or
just any group of people that are gonna
buy from you at some time okay
they all exist on these platforms right
now
they're all there
and what's crazy is
in 2022
all of these platforms are driven
by something called artificial
intelligence
okay
and you don't have to understand
artificial intelligence to be able to
use it just by posting on
instagram or facebook
or tick tock
or even
on your blog google
and even email lists
there's artificial intelligence that's
deciding
who to show your content to okay
and so what you want to do is you learn
how to train the ai
to show your content to the right people
and so that's what we're doing that's
that's the process that i'm going to
walk you through is training
the ai
to find you customers
and it's not as complicated as it sounds
you don't need to know code
you don't need to know how to code
anything
it actually has to do with the words
that you say and i break this down a lot
in a lot of the content that i've
created
and so one of the best steps to train
the ai
is with
two forms
organic content
and paid advertising
okay
so you have organic content that goes on
these platforms and you have paid
advertising that goes on these platforms
and they work together
to train
your unique artificial intelligence
now your ai doesn't like exist somewhere
it exists and what you get to do is
these platforms give you an opportunity
to go in there and create buckets okay
and so what we do is we create a bucket
of who we are able to reach
with our paid ads
and with our organic content
okay so this bucket of people
this is this is a bucket of people right
here
that are most likely to be
out of the 8 billion people right
and how many people are actually on the
internet let's actually find that
statistic real quick because i want to
actually use some real numbers here
how many internet users are there in
the world
56 of the world population okay so
you're looking at four billion people
are on these platforms okay
what you want is your bucket includes
five percent
of those four billion people
okay so we got four billion
uh times let's see what five percent of
that is
200 million okay
so there's about 200 million people in
your bucket
right here
and what what's going to happen is
the algorithms
in fact i can see this when i go into my
page on social media it actually tells
me my my average audience size for my
content is right around 250 million
okay
and so
out of that 200 million the algorithm
already knows who those 200 million
people are
so so what what it does is
it doesn't even
care about
the other
3.8 billion people
that are not in that bucket
okay
so there's 3.8 billion people
that you'll probably never reach
unless you become like you know
president of a country or something
which is not far-fetched i actually know
some people that could be on that that
trajectory
i have some friends that i've walked
through this process that
i would not be surprised if one of them
campaigns for
presidency in the next
upcoming
20 30 years
literally
by using this process but they started
with this process okay
now here's where it gets interesting
out of this group of people the 200
million people
you then want to find
what is your true buyer
base
okay so your true buyer base is five
percent of the five percent of everybody
okay
and so five percent
of the five percent
is 10 million
and this 10 million group of people
is people that like they are they will
be obsessed with you
with everything that you do
everything that you offer
like they will live and breathe what it
is that you put out there so there's a
potential
group of
10 million buyers
for every single person out there i
truly believe that and so what it is is
you can train the ai
to instead of it wasting time and
showing your ads and showing your
content to 200 million people
the better you train it it starts
showing it
to these 10 million people
and it ends up not showing it to about
190 million that are probably not going
to become your buyers
these 10 million will end up sharing it
with the other 190 million
by word of mouth eventually
okay but these 10 million become your
your most
committed people
and so just by you it all starts with
making organic content
on facebook tick tock and instagram
and then running paid ads
and so what you're able to do is you're
able to run those ads
to that group of 10 million people
and i walk you through how to create we
call them look-alike audiences
or artificial intelligence audiences
and so the words that you say
how you say it
will
train the algorithm to show your content
to the right people most people just
don't know how to use the right words
they don't know how to say the right
words and so that's why we use a tool
like jasper.ai
ai actually helps us write the right
words
okay
that way you don't actually have to know
exactly how to market to these people
to reach them jasper ai you can tell it
what your product is what you offer and
jasper ai will help you write and craft
content it's strategically designed to
use artificial intelligence to reverse
engineer these algorithms to be able to
find those 10 million people
and that's where it gets fun okay
so what you do is
this is all
your your organic content your paid ads
right here
now what you have is what we call your
your
your irresistible
offer
okay
so your irresistible offer
is something
that
five percent
of the 10 million people
right here
okay
it's about 200 000 people
i think
to do some quick math i'm not i'm not
super good at math in my brain 500 000
people yeah 500 000 people
half a million people
you want to create an irresistible offer
that half a million people
find it impossible
to say no to
okay
and you want to give those half a
million people that offer for free
now your offer could be
a free event
a free
master class
a free webinar
a free ebook
it could even be a book on amazon that
you sell for a dollar or or ten dollars
okay
so what you're trying to do is you're
trying to get these 500 000 people to
get on your email list
right you're going to reach about 10
million people with your content your
paid ads but only about half a million
of them are ever gonna actually take the
next step with you
about five percent
and really it's more like two percent
for most people
two to five percent especially in the
beginning
it'll be about two percent
so we bring this number down to two
hundred thousand
two percent are going to sign up and
join your email list
out of the eight billion people
and this all happens by writing the
words
that attract people and creating an
irresistible offer and putting it out
there in your your organic content and
your paid ads
to get people on your email list
and you bribe them you ethically bribe
them
with
a free class
a free training
a free ebook
or or some kind of a cheap book of some
kind some or an event of some kind
to get them to sign up to engage with
you okay
another format of this actually a
podcast actually is part of this
it's funny i'm like i'm recording a
podcast right now and i forgot about
that
podcast
uh but but a podcast people aren't
actually
giving you their information so your
podcast or your blog post still go back
to
it being organic content because people
haven't given you their email address
they haven't signed up for something yet
with you okay
so
you're directing people
from here
from your organic content
this is the ether of people again break
this down
8 billion people there's only about 4
billion that are actually on the
internet
there's only about 200 million
that will
ever really be qualified for what you
offer
unless you're selling something like an
iphone
right
or or a product that everybody
can use
health products might be a little
different but again
there might only be 200 million people
that really need the exact health
product that you offer
okay
so we're segmenting we're categorizing
these people this is what we call our
niche and the ai helps us find
the people that are in that niche
and so you create an irresistible offer
to put out there
to the people that listen to your
podcast to check out your blog post that
engage with your organic content
and engage with your paid advertising
and so and and the goal is an email list
that has about 200 to 500 000 people
this is not unlikely
a number of our clients rick pino
um
my mom sandy kurkowski
have that many people on on email lists
right
and so
those are like the most
engaged people
because they've said yes i want more of
what you offer and i want to go on a
journey with you okay
and so this is really
your goal with all of this
right here
is not to bring transformation to
people's lives unfortunately it's where
a lot of people miss it when it comes to
their coaching their course creation
their training and their books as
they're trying to change people's lives
with this stuff
you'll impact people i've had a lot of
people impacted by this podcast but
ultimately the people who actually sign
up with me for something
get on my email list buy my courses
become a paid one-on-one coaching client
they get the transformation so i craft
and design
all of my
organic content and paid advertising and
offers around
what these people care about
and i'm running my paid ads specifically
to this irresistible offer okay so we're
running paid ads
to the irresistible offer
and we're able to train the ai based off
of how many people visit your website
how many people listen to your episodes
how many people engage with your organic
content
and we're able to if we don't know what
words to say we're able to use tools
like jasper ai to come up with those
words so are you getting this
if any part of this you're stuck on i'd
love for you to write me
send me a message leave a comment below
and i can make additional podcast
episodes off of what part of this that i
just went over that you're stuck on okay
and i'm gonna include additional
trainings that break down the nuances of
all this for you
the courses at my website break down in
depth i have a course over at my website
called irresistible offers that sell
where i break down
how to create that irresistible offer
right here
we have a course called social media
content creation made that social media
content creation yeah that's for organic
content right
and then we have a course called social
media ads that work
this is for paid ads
we also show you how to build your
website how to create a coaching program
how to create your own online courses
you can get a bundle of all my courses
on here as well
or go through the podcast go through the
different blog posts on my website
and learn at your own pace that way okay
so your goal is you want to get as many
people as possible
into an irresistible offer of some kind
so your goal is you want to get as many
people as possible into
your irresistible offer of some kind
to get on your email list
to engage with you okay
now what are you doing in
your event in your master class in your
webinar
in your
ebook
uh
blog posts your podcast all of that
okay
so this part of the process
is the same
for all of these that are your
irresistible offers
don't get overwhelmed and overthink okay
which one should i do
i'm going to create an additional
podcast episode here in the coming weeks
where i break down specifically what to
put in your free offer but i'm going to
summarize that here real quick so your
free offer the intention is
you want it to be irresistible for the
result that somebody has to the problem
that's in their life and so you want to
expose some kind of a problem that your
product or service solves
and you want to get people this to to
sign up to find the answer and the
solution to that problem
now some of you might be saying well i
don't want to give them the solution for
free and that mindset is wrong
you need to give people solutions for
free
but only up to the point of their
comprehension
okay like right now i'm giving you the
blueprint for free i give you the
blueprint for free and yet i still have
people who buy my coaching because they
need to understand the nuances where i
walk them through based on individually
what they need help with
so you want to give your best content
away for free
in this
what you want to be careful of though is
you don't want to
give too much that it overwhelms people
okay
so you want to keep it simple enough
that it's not going to overwhelm your
target customer
so how do we turn
200 000
into 300 buyers
well what you're going to end up finding
is out of this 200 000 people
and we really need to shrink those
numbers right
you're gonna have about three percent
of these people become buyers
so out of two hundred thousand
three to five percent
you'll have about six
to ten thousand
become your customers
okay
now we shrink these numbers down because
a lot of times this is based off of how
much you can actually spend on paid
advertising
you'll know that you maxed out an offer
a paid offer a paid product of some kind
when you have about ten thousand buyers
of one product now i've seen a lot of
products as you get better at this
you might have
fifty thousand or even a hundred
thousand buyers
but that usually doesn't happen in the
beginning okay it just doesn't
because what you're going to find is
through this process
you're going to discover
a new
way
of communicating what you do to people
with people
have you sold ten thousand products
before i have
we've sold
over fifty thousand
with one business
and what we found is we ended up
reinventing this whole process about
five times
creating new offers creating a new angle
to do our social media content
as you go through this process you'll
end up actually reinventing most of this
every six to 12 months
as you get more clear and more focused
now why are you doing that you might say
well if i did all this work and it's
making me money why would i do it again
and change it and make it change it
because you'll actually make more money
by changing it and you would be choosing
to make less money by not doing so
okay
so you're going to make more money by
optimizing this process
as you start to get buyers what you
don't want to do and i see a lot of
people do this is optimizing the process
before they have anybody buying from
them
you want to test out your funnel
you want to put it out there you want to
get some buyers now if you're not
getting any buyers something's got to
change
something's got to change
if you spent at least a thousand dollars
on paid advertising and nobody bought
anything from you let's say your product
is 97 bucks or something like that you
know there's also the value ladder like
what do we charge for our products
and i broke that down i'm actually let
me find the page where i break that down
here
i have it i did it on another training
so i'm gonna
pull it back up here for you
okay so the value ladder is right here
okay
so
your social media this is your free
content
so
this range right here
this is where you're gonna be able to
get
between
six and fifty thousand buyers easily
is selling products from a dollar up to
297 bucks
anything under 300
you'll be able to
sell that many people you're gonna sell
a lot less of the high ticket stuff and
and high ticket is where you end up
making more of your profits okay
selling stuff that's in the two to fifty
thousand dollar range to people
so you might have
ten thousand people
in the beginning you might have 300
right
or 3 000.
let's just use for the sake of the
example 300 people
bought a
47 product from you okay
[Music]
about
three percent of those people
of the 300.
300 times
there's about 10 people
would be willing to invest about a
thousand dollars with you okay
so you have 300 right here
and you have about 10 of those people
that will invest a thousand
so that's 10 grand so you look at okay
times 47 bucks that's 14 000 right that
pays for your advertising
most of you are going to end up breaking
even on your advertising at this level
and i see a lot of people get really
bent out of shape about that that
they're breaking even selling products
for 297 bucks that's by design because
your goal is and you want to move people
further up your value ladder okay
and here's how it happens
then you'll get about ten thousand
dollars at this level that's your profit
margin
and you might have one of those people
be willing to pay you between two and
ten thousand dollars so you'll end up
basically doubling or tripling down your
money
that you broke even on on higher ticket
stuff and most of you if your course
graders or coaches need to stop giving
away your stuff for cheap and have
higher ticket offerings for people for
people that want that next step
at my website my higher ticket offering
is my one-on-one coaching okay
so i have my courses they're about 500
bucks each course
and then i have one-on-one coaching
right here where i come alongside you
and help you build your business
and we have a number of customer
testimonies of one-on-one coaching
clients
but i sell that for seventy five hundred
dollars okay
for twelve sessions and we break down
and i help you build all of this
together okay let's go back to the last
page here
the one that we were just working on
to break this down
so your goal
is you want to move people
from these
you know
one dollar seven dollars some of you
when you're gonna get started
just charge a dollar or seven bucks just
to test it out
if you can get somebody to give you
seven bucks you've validated that
there's an there's a desire for what you
offer
and you can test that out with your free
content as well if you're not getting
anybody signing up with their email
address for something for free
there's not a desire for what you're
actually offering or you're not
explaining it in a way that people
actually want so you want to use jasper
to help you come up with better words
so out of this group of people right
here then you're gonna have that three
percent three to five percent
who are gonna end up buying something
from you that's maybe a thousand dollars
and that's your profit margins right
there
okay
and so most of you in your business
could do this every single month
and then and end up making
20 to 40 000 a month in your
business in the beginning
you get it
as a profit margin because the idea is
you run this cycle every two weeks
so you basically end up trying to get
three to six hundred people to give you
seven bucks and then
upgrade
three to five percent of them
ten to twenty of those people
to a thousand dollar program something
like that
and go up the ladder
again that's why you have to charge more
of what you're offering now what we're
finding is once you optimize this you're
actually not going to break even on this
level you can usually double your ad
spend on this level and then triple and
quadruple right here
and that's where the clients that are
really getting the most results with us
are are maxing it out they're not
breaking even on their 47 they're
actually doubling their money on that
level okay so they're end up they they
end up maybe spending
you know seven seven thousand on
paid ads
now before you shut your brain down
that 7 000 you're going to be able to
end up paying back
right away
put it on a credit card you end up
making a payment right to the credit
card
right away
because if you're using stripe
you can do instant payouts
where the money comes in and then you
send it right to your credit card to pay
off the ad spend so it's not actually
money that you had out of pocket and you
budget it over the course of a couple of
days so we usually start with
you know
ten dollars a day in ads fifty dollars a
day in ads
and then you end up making back twenty
to a hundred dollars of that you end up
profiting
you start adjusting your budget to where
that is if you're losing money running
ads you're running them the wrong way
you just are
you want to at least be breaking even so
that you can take the money that's
coming in on the front end initially
right away within seven days
within seven days to be able to pay off
that ad spend
and then
in that seven day cycle 14 day cycle
you're then upgrading people to that
thousand dollar level with you
okay
[Music]
and then usually over the course of
maybe the next two to three months they
might upgrade to to something that's
about five to ten grand
and that's where the money really starts
coming in and that's where that's that's
the seven figure business level
right here
okay
so you build out your value ladder
what's what is the next step that i can
offer people in this
so in your free irresistible offer
in your free irresistible offer
you're sending people to buy
something along this list
now here's the cool thing this is an
interesting part of this an interesting
part of the science of this the longer
in length of time that you're talking
the the higher price you can actually
sell something to people when you do a
pitch
so the longer that somebody sits with
you to learn something from you
the more you can actually charge for
what your pitch is
okay
so like if your master class is only 30
minutes you maybe could sell a 47 to 97
product
if your master class is two hours long
you could actually sell a thousand
dollar product usually to the people
that made it all the way through the
two-hour deal with you
if you do an event that's a three day or
a five day or even a 10 day event where
you do an hour each day the people that
make it to the end of that event they
might be even be able to give you two to
five thousand dollars right there
and that becomes your cycle so you run
an irresistible offer
to the people that are out here
to send them to your paid offer and you
move them up your value ladder to buy
from you
and that's your sales funnel and you use
persuasive language you become better at
sales you can become better at your
presentation
i talk about books like the way of the
wolf by jordan belfort never split the
difference by chris voss
these are two books that'll really help
you become better at your sales pitch
and so your goal is how can i connect
with
as many people as possible
that are most likely to become
a buyer of something that i put out
there
and you move them up that funnel okay
and that's how you go from ad
to sale
and make a profit
in this business
all right
now again i know some of you might have
some different questions on this
concerns ideas
anybody can do this
any excuse that you give yourself for
why you believe that you can't do this
is a lie that you're believing in your
head right now
it is you might be saying jeremiah i
don't have seven thousand dollars
like the fact that your brain is
focusing on that is crazy to me
when i just showed you a path to make
seven
seven figures
you don't need it all up front
you spend ten dollars a day do you got
10 bucks
well no i don't have 10 bucks well if
you don't have 10 bucks then you're not
in the right place listening to me
you're just not
and then your goal is okay i i i got 10
bucks i made back 10 bucks
i got 10 bucks i made back 20 bucks now
i can reinvest that
into
okay i made 20 bucks now we can put 20
into our ads
and then that snowballs like that
to where then you grow to that level
so many people don't do this
because they're like i'm not here yet
with seven thousand dollars my friends
you're you're stuck on the wrong thing
are you even making content for your
social media yet the answer is most of
you that are stuck on i don't have seven
thousand dollars aren't even making
social media content
daily
and then that brings up a whole another
list of excuses i don't have time to
make content every single day i'm sorry
but you do
it only takes it's again any excuse and
reason that you come up with why you
can't do this is a lie that you're
believing that you've convinced yourself
of
it is
my content takes me five minutes a day
to make
i recorded on my phone like this
to get people to buy from you you have
to know how to
find the right people that are out there
in the ether of the internet there's
about four billion people online and
move them along a path to qualify them
as buyers
for you i have a podcast episode coming
out this next week where i break that
down this whole topic right here might
be kind of hard to see right here about
how to do this check that out at my
website the grow your life podcast i
think it's really going to help you walk
you through the sales funnel process
start to finish from ad to sale i'll see
you on that podcast episode see so that
took me 30 seconds to record a piece of
content that i'm gonna put on tiktok and
instagram
if you're taking longer than five
minutes to come up with your your free
social media content you're spending way
too long and you're stuck in your head
and you're too focused on being perfect
and saying the perfect thing and it
being the perfect thing and you have to
get rid of that perfectionism is the
greatest
detriment to business owners being
successful because they're so focused on
it has to be a specific way or i'll do
nothing at all and they get stuck in
their brain because they feel like it's
not safe to put something out there
that's anything less than perfect
so deal with that some of you might need
to talk to a therapist through through
that as to why you perfectionism
is is such a big important part of your
life and that you literally won't do any
of what i talked about some of you are
watching this right now you've been
hearing me talk about this for three to
five years still haven't done anything
because you're stuck on i don't know
what to say on my social media content
three to five years i know people right
now
three to five years that are stuck on
that
that's what this course social media
content creation made easy is all about
finally never have to wonder what should
i post again
but let's go over to my youtube channel
and we'll type in
content
literally i have videos for free on my
youtube channel that answer this topic
of what should i put on my social media
content
never run out of ideas for content
creating content that sells when you
struggle to make content document easy
trick to make like i have made so much
content about making content
and yet people still say i don't know
what to say and make content about
maybe stop making that be your excuse
and reason why you're failing and and
and maybe
you you're living your life needing some
kind of a crutch
because it makes you feel better instead
of taking personal responsibility to say
i'm scared to do this
i'm scared of reaching that many people
i'm scared of what people might say
about me
i'm scared of not being good enough
again i get that
that's why your belief in yourself is
the number one thing that's going to
have an impact on this process
how much you believe in yourself and
what you offer if you don't believe in
yourself you're never going to make
anything because you're physically and
mentally incapable of doing any of this
if you don't believe in yourself you're
just not
your brain will self-sabotage you every
step of the way
and so
working on your self-esteem is one of
the greatest things that you can do
okay
and again i have a
type in go to go to my my youtube
type in jeremiahkowski self-esteem what
i do when i scared and lack confidence
self-belief determines your income when
self doubt creeps in stop being so self
critical self belief in business healthy
self worth lack of confidence my friends
listen i'm not saying this to make you
feel inadequate
i'm saying this to tell you that you
no longer need to make these be your
crutch and your excuse for why you can't
build your business
there's a path there's a process i
provide resources for you for free that
can help break you out of the cycle for
any step on this process that you're
stuck
you just have to do the work and listen
if you're not
i know i know for a fact i know the
statistics
only about five percent of you listening
to this podcast right now
are ever going to even start making
social media content
the other 95 of you are going to come up
with reasons and excuses for why it's
impossible for you and you're going to
be at the same place that you are five
years from now
unless something changes
unless you decide i'm done with
making excuses for why i can't i'm done
with
coming up with reasons for why i can't
and instead i start believing i can i am
capable i am worth putting myself out
there i can impact people i can make a
difference and i'm not gonna let the
fear and worry of what anybody thinks
about me stop me along the way i'm not
gonna let the fear and worry of haters
and rude people stop me i'm gonna work
on myself i'm gonna work on my
self-belief i'm gonna work on my fear
and worry i'm gonna work on healing the
trauma and the fact that maybe i was
verbally abused and and that when people
speak certain things to me it triggers
me and it hurts me and i'm afraid of
people saying that stuff online to me
because i know that that's a problem
that most people have that stops them
and instead growing
accepting yourself for who you are
loving yourself enough to say you know
what
for the future of my family for the
future generations that are out there
i'm going to step up and do something
different
choice is yours my friends
what are you gonna choose
thanks for listening to this podcast i'm
so glad that you were here i'm so glad
that you made it to the end of this
you're the cream of the crop
most people
i have the statistics on it i literally
see the data of how many people start a
podcast episode with me and don't make
it to the end
if you've made it all the way to the end
of this you have what it takes to be
successful you just have to start to put
it into action
plug into this podcast plug into the
videos on my social media
purchase my courses consider scheduling
a free 45-minute discovery call and
let's talk about one-on-one coaching
together
you can go to my website if you scroll
all the way down to the bottom of my
site you're going to see right here
schedule a 45-minute discovery call
and you can actually schedule this with
me if you're somebody that's serious
about one-on-one coaching you and i can
talk together
about
your business where you're at help you
get unstuck and help you get started
building your business together
grow your life everybody
we'll talk soon have a good one